ucoincash.co 2018-09-15

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes how Ucoin Cash and affiliated partners (“Ucoin Cash,” “we” or “us”) collect, use and share information about you. This policy applies to information we collect when you use our websites, including www.ucoincash.co, (collectively, the “Site”) or otherwise interact with us as described below. 

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of this policy, and in some cases, we may provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to the homepages of our Site or sending you an email notification). We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy whenever you interact with us to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy. 

COLLECTION OF INFORMATION 

_Information You Provide to Us_

We collect information you provide directly to us. For example, we collect information when you create an online account, post messages to our forums or wikis or otherwise communicate with us. 

The types of information we may collect include your name, email address, username, password, location and any other information you choose to provide. 

INFORMATION WE COLLECT AUTOMATICALLY 

We automatically collect certain information about you when you access or use our Site or transact business with us, including Log Information. We collect information about your use of our Site, including the type of browser you use, access times, pages viewed, your IP address and the page you visited before navigating to our Site. 

Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies: We may use cookies, web beacons (also known as “tracking pixels”) and other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you interact with our Site or emails, including information about your browsing behavior on our Site. We use this information to improve our Site and your experience, see which areas and features of our sites are popular, count visits, understand campaign effectiveness and determine whether an email has been opened and links within the email have been clicked. 

INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM OTHER SOURCES 

We may also obtain information about you from other sources and combine that with information we collect about you. 

USE OF INFORMATION 

We may use information about you for various purposes, including to: 

• Respond to your comments, questions and requests and provide customer service 

• Monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in order to operate and improve our Site 

• Manage your online account(s) and send you technical notices, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages 

• Link or combine with information we get from others to help understand your needs and provide you with better service, and 

• Carry out any other purpose for which the information was collected. 

SHARING OF INFORMATION 

We may share information about you as follows: 

• With vendors, consultants and other service providers who need access to such information to carry out work on our behalf. 

• In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with any applicable law, regulation or legal process, or as otherwise required by any applicable law, rule or regulation. 

• If we believe your actions are inconsistent with our user agreements or policies, or to protect the rights, property and safety of us or any third party. 

• In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company, and 

• With your consent or at your direction. 

We may also share aggregated or de-identified information, which cannot reasonably be used to identify you. 

ANALYTICS SERVICES PROVIDED BY OTHERS 

We engage third parties to provide analytics services. These entities may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to collect information about your use of our Site, including your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages, links clicked and conversion information. This information may be used by us and others to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content and better understand your online activity. 

SECURITY 

We take reasonable measures to help protect information about you from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. 

YOUR CHOICES 

_Account Information_

You may update, correct or delete your online account information at any time by logging into your account or by contacting us at the information below. Please note that we may retain certain information as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may also retain cached or archived copies of information about you for a certain period of time. 

COOKIES 

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually set your browser to remove or reject cookies, but note that doing so does not necessarily affect third party flash cookies used in connection with our Site. If you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of our Site. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy contact us at [support@ucoincash.co](mailto:support@ucoincash.co)
